Finding Aid for Austin Blair Family Papers 1849-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Miscellaneous
  - Blair Family genealogical chart (Folder UAm)
  - Portrait of Austin and Sarah Horton Blair's four sons: George Horton, Charles A., Fred Johnson and Austin True, taken for their mother 1894 (Folder UAm)
  - Print of Austin Blair (Folder UAm)
  - Portrait of the Jackson County Bar Association Meeting, including Charles A. Blair (Folder UAm)
  - Mysterious photograph of unidentified girl in front of a house (Folder UAm)
  - Portrait of Horace Greeley with two other men (Folder UAm)